🎉🎉🎉Hello, Client, How are you?🎉🎉🎉

Hello, Clients.

Being a Full Stack Developer, I’m highly skillful in developing both the front and backend of the websites. Over the years, I have provided technical support to multiple customers which has further improved my web development skills and enabled me to complete my tasks efficiently.

I have worked for 6 years with MERN stack and am focus to Angular and Next.js technologies  recently. I have rich experinces and knowledgements of NPM, Redux, Babel, Webpack. I've ever make some sites to be possible to run without relation of browsers' version by using webpack and babel, and composed the projects from scratch.
Using my set of skills and experience, I would love to make you an amazing website which will certainly meet all your professional expectations.
I am familiar with building clean, efficient, well-documented, well-structured, high-quality code projects. Also, I am very well-versed in the agile approach in project development and really love to add my creativity to the overall project implementation.

✨ My skills:
I can help you with the following skills to achieve your goal.
My Skills:
✪ Front End programming: React.js, Next.js Angular
✪ Online Stores: Shopify, WooCommerce, Opencart, Magento.
✪ HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, Javascript, Python.
✪ PHP, Laravel, Codeigniter, ZendFramework, Drupal.
✪ CMS: WordPress, Shopify, Magento, Django, Drupal.
✪ MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Database Programming.
✪ MERN Stack(MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js)

My past React projects are as follows(Please check these!!!):
⚡http://yourcontour.com/en 
⚡https://www.boutiqat.com/ 
⚡https://sposadresses.com/ 
⚡https://www.voxnclothing.com/ 
⚡http://www.shopsupergurl.com/ 

My github url is "forever78419"
I have read your job description carefully, and it's a very interesting job for me.
I ensure the highest quality of product and 100% satisfaction through my work.
I also can work on your time zone during work and work in 40hrs every week.
Furthermore, I hope really to work with you.
If you are interesting to me, please let us discuss more detail on chat.

Thank you.

Authenticity and creativity are defining characteristics of me. 
I continuously improve my knowledge, and I train myself.


/////////////////



Hello, Client, how are you?

I have read your job description carefully and it's very interesting job for me.
I'm a professional Full-Stack developer, and I have 8+ years of experience with Frontend & Backend Development & Amazon web service.

My Strong Experiences are as follows:
• Django/Python
• ReactJS/Redux
• React Native
• Next.JS
• Vue/Vuex
• PHP(Laravel, CodeIgniter)
• WordPress
• HTML/SASS/CSS
• PostgreSQL/Mongo/MySQL Database
• CSSFramework like Bootstrap, Material UI, Semantic UI, etc…
• NodeJS
• Backend Rest API
• AWS Web Service
• AWS Elastic Beanstalk/EC2
• Payment Integration

You can see my past projects on these url:
https://simplychocolate.dk/ (React.js,NextJS,Laravel, MySQL)
https://www.echopark.com(WordPress, PostgreSQL)
https://www.honorvettech.com/ (Vue.js, Next.js, Node.js, Express)

I ensure the highest quality of product and 100% satisfaction through my work.
I also can work on your time zone during work and reply on your request all the time.
I hope really to work with you.
If you are interesting to me, please let us discuss more detail on chat.

Thank you.



////////////// 



I



//////////// Backend and FrontEnd Developing //////////////

⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Hello, Client, How are you?
I have worked for 6 years with MERN stack and am focus to Angular and Next.js technologies  recently. I've ever composed the projects from scratch by separating Front-End and Back-End. During development, I've implemented Creating sign up, sign in, password change, authentication perfectly and provided modularity, reusability.
In this way, in several times I completed perfect and smooth SPA(Single Page Application) by using Node, React Library, Express Framework, MongoDB, so I've made my clients to be satisfied.
Using my set of skills and experience, I would love to make you an amazing website which will certainly meet all your professional expectations.
I am familiar with building clean, efficient, well-documented, well-structured, high-quality code projects. Also, I am very well-versed in the agile approach in project development and really love to add my creativity to the overall project implementation.

✨ My skills:
I can help you with the following skills to achieve your goal.
My Skills:
✪ MERN Stack(MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js)
✪ Front End programming: React.js, Next.js Angular
✪ Online Stores: Shopify, WooCommerce, Opencart, Magento.
✪ HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, Javascript, Python.
✪ CMS: WordPress, Shopify, Magento, Django, Drupal.
✪ MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL.


My past React projects are as follows(Please check these!!!):
⚡http://yourcontour.com/en 
⚡https://www.boutiqat.com/ 
⚡https://sposadresses.com/ 
⚡https://www.voxnclothing.com/ 
⚡http://www.shopsupergurl.com/ 

I ensure the highest quality of product and 100% satisfaction through my work.
I also can work on your time zone during work and work in 40hrs every week.
Furthermore, I hope really to work with you.
If you are interesting to me, please let us discuss more detail on chat.

Thank you.

############################## Full Stack Developer with MongoDB #################


⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Hello, Client, How are you?
I'm an expert developer with 10+ years of IT experience, designing and developing solid, reliable, scalable and maintainable software solutions in MERN stack. I have ability to prioritize well, communicate clearly, able to work across multiple facets of the project .Also, I have strong analytic capability and the ability to create innovative solutions.

I have a consistent track record of delivery and excellent software engineering skills with good practice of software architecture, mastery of software development life cycle, and proficiency in planning, analysis, documentation,  programming, bug fixing, refactoring, testing, deployment and maintenance.

+ JavaScript
+ TypeScript
+ Node.JS Next.js, and Express.js
+ React.js
+ Redux, Redux-Thunk
+ Apollo GraphQL
+ MongoDB, AWS amplify, MySQL
+ Bootstrap4
+ Gulp, WebPack, Grunt
+ Git

SUMMARY:

+Expertise in developing web pages using HTML5, CSS3, MVC, JavaScript, ES6, JQuery, JSON, XML.
+Expertise in creating the user validation forms and using the RESTful services for sending the data to the server.
+Strong experience with the version controls GIT, GITHUB, Bit Bucket, SVN and Package manager NPM.

I also will work on your time zone during work and work in 40hrs every week.
I do monitoring of full project life-cycle development from Client communication until the project completion and work collaboratively in all functional areas to ensure deliveries to the client satisfaction.

Thank you.


####Wprdpress
https://spectruss.com
https://growthplay.com/
https://www.abaeternowatches.com/
http://www.protest.eu/
http://www.birdsonggregory.com/

http://www.cityscopemag.com/
https://thelaranyc.com/
http://www.easyweddings.com.au/
http://nouba.com.au/
https://addepar.com/
http://www.pluginnc.com/
http://heritageprep.org/
https://nurturelife.com/
http://triumgroup.com/
https://fordplantation.com/
http://ataboystudios.com
	shoptheshop.etam.com
	preprod-lovers.vogue.fr
http://www.faradaybikes.com/

I am a full-stack developer who has over 10 years of experience in web, mobile & software development.
As a full-stack developer, I specialized in everything from front-end to back-end and have a general knowledge of all steps from concept to finished product.

🏆 My skillsets are the following:

💎 JavaScript Frameworks
- Front-end: React.js/Next.js, Angular, Vue.js/Nuxt.js
- Back-end: Node.js/Express.js

💎 PHP: Laravel, CodeIgniter
💎 Python: Django, Webapp2
💎 .NET Framework : .NET Core, ASP.NET, C#.NET, VB.NET

💎 Database
- Relational Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MSSQL
- NoSQL Databases: MongoDB, Firebase, Amazon DynamoDB

💎 Web Service Platforms
- Amazon Web Service
- Google Cloud Platform
- Microsoft Azure
- Heroku

👍 Benefits of working with me
➀ I am 24/7 online for communication with you, so you can check the progress of your project any time you want.
➁ You will get a well-structured, clean, and fully-commented project.
➂ I provide full maintenance and troubleshooting of the project.
➃ I deliver all reports and documentation about the project if you want.
➄ I speak English very fluently, so you will not feel the language barrier. 



#################### MERN Stack Proposal 1 ##########################

⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ How are you, Clients.
I am Anton Mikhailov, experienced freelancer from Ukraine and I am 31 years old.
I've spent the last 8 years specializing in javascript learning how to use modern and classic design pattern in an architecture, how to capitalize on JS's strong parts and avoid the bad parts, how to use certain framework making sure they work correctly, how to optimize code to perform better. I have solid experiences completed full stack applications with react.js, redux, graphQL, SASS from scratch. I have ever developed MERN Stack projects related to Socket by using node module called WebRTC.

I will design new or continue working on existing project, and I am comfortable working alone or with an existing team of any size. I'm able to interface and communicate with non-technical staff when necessary. I will always try to stick to best practices unless job requires otherwise.

I am skilled in:
💎 Server side: Node.js (ExpressJS, NextJS)
💎 Client side:  Reactjs/Redux/Hook, Es6, Typescript, React-native, Javascript, jQuery, WebRTC, babel, webpack, D3.js, AJAX, HTML5, CSS3, JSON, XML, NPM, Yarn.
💎 UnitTesting: mocha, jest.
💎 Databases: MongoDB, PostgresQL, graphQL, SQLite, NoSQL, MySQL
💎 Software Content Management: Git, Github, Heroku, SVN, trello, bitbucket.
💎 Miscellaneous APIs: Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Google Map, Google Custom Search, Youtube, Linkedin, oAuth, PayPal checkouts(all kind), amazon checkout and alot more.
💎 Web Service Platforms
- Amazon Web Service
- Google Cloud Platform
- Microsoft Azure
- Heroku

👍 Benefits of working with me
➀ I am 24/7 online for communication with you, so you can check the progress of your project any time you want.
➁ You will get a well-structured, clean, and fully-commented project.
➂ I provide full maintenance and troubleshooting of the project.
➃ I deliver all reports and documentation about the project if you want.
➄ I have strong teamwork skill and experience designing and building large and complex, maintainable structure in my past projects.

"The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams." -Eleanor Roosevelt

Thank you.

#################### MERN Stack Proposal 2 ##########################

Hello, Clients.
I'm an expert developer with 10+ years of IT experience, designing and developing solid, reliable, scalable and maintainable software solutions in MERN stack. I have ability to prioritize well, communicate clearly, able to work across multiple facets of the project and juggle multiple responsibilities at the same time. Also, I have strong analytic capability and the ability to create innovative solutions.

I have a consistent track record of delivery and excellent software engineering skills with good practice of software architecture, mastery of software development life cycle, and proficiency in planning, analysis, documentation, prototyping, programming, bug fixing, refactoring, testing, deployment and maintenance.

+ JavaScript
+ TypeScript
+ Node.JS Next.js, and Express.js
+ React.js, HTML, shopify, UI/UX
+ Redux, Redux-Thunk
+ Apollo GraphQL
+ MongoDB, AWS amplify, MySQL
+ Bootstrap4, jQuery
+ Gulp, WebPack, Grunt
+ Git

SUMMARY:

+Expertise in developing web pages using HTML5, CSS3, MVC, SASS, LESS, JavaScript, ES6, JQuery, JSON, XML.
+Expertise in creating the user validation forms and using the RESTful services for sending the data to the server.
+Strong experience with the version controls GIT, GITHUB, Bit Bucket, SVN and Package manager NPM

👍 Benefits of working with me
➀ I am 24/7 online for communication with you, so you can check the progress of your project any time you want.
➁ You will get a well-structured, clean, and fully-commented project.
➂ I provide full maintenance and troubleshooting of the project.
➃ I deliver all reports and documentation about the project if you want.

Thank you.


####################### PHP #######################

Hello,
Warm Greetings!! 

 I read your job description completely and I found my skills relevant to your project. I am a professional web developer with 5 years of programming experience for a multitude of different technology projects. I have no work right now so I will go the extra mile to get the job done. And provide you 100% GUARANTEED Satisfaction. 

I am skilled in Core PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JQuery, JavaScript.React.js, Vue. js, Node.js  I have worked on many PHP-related CMS like.. WordPress, Laravel, CI.Experience with integrating third-party SOAP, REST, JSON APIs.    

>>Additionally, in my work history I have:- 

I implemented code based on project specifications.
Created new tables within MySQL Tested and documented code Provided feedback to the development group to improve Agile Project management methods.

 Look at my previous work samples:- 

https://www.moschino.com/us_en/ (SHOPPING SITE)(PHP 7.0.1)  
http://pinpoint.promo
https://www.neurosurgerycost.com/ 
https://finder.weedreader.com/ (laravel) 

 Looking for the soonest reply from you.  

Regards


################## React, Django ####################

Hello, Dear.
I have more than 7+ years of experience developing, coding, and testing Full-stack, Backend, Frontend Development.
With my rich experience in write reusable, testable, and efficient code that meets our clients’ needs and integrating user-facing elements into applications, I think I would be a great addition to your business.
I also have excellent teamwork skills and collaborate closely with the development team.
I can also bring my skills to help you improve on existing products as well as build new solutions.
My main expert skills are following:
- Back-end: Python, Django, Flask, MVC, MVT, .NET, C/C++, PHP, Golang
- ORM, MySQL, MongoDB, Google Firebase, GraphQL, AWS
- Front-end technologies: React.js, Redux, React Native, TypeScript, Vue.js, Vuex, Angularjs, HTML/HTML5/CSS, Node.js, Express
- variety web frameworks: Laravel, CodeIgniter
- AI and Machine Learning
- Strong version control
- Good communication
- Blockchain, Smart Contract, Cryptography, Web3.js
I am ready to start work immediately,I’m available for working with you for 8 hours/day and dedicate 40 hours/week to your work on available in any time zone that suits you most.
I look forward to speaking with you soon.
Sincerely,

################## React, Django ####################

⭐⭐⭐ Hello, Dear ⭐⭐⭐

I have read your requirements carefully and I think I can finish this well enough.
I am a senior full stack developer with over 8 years of backend and frontend development experience.
In the process, many projects have been completed and we have seen customers satisfied.
If you want some examples, I'll be happy to show them.
I'm sure your project can be successful too.

My skill is:
✔️ FrontEnd
ReactJS, AngularJS, VueJS, HTML, HTML5, CSS, WordPress, Shopify
✔️ BackEnd
Node.js, Express, PHP, Next.js, CI, Laravel, Django
✔️ Database
Firebase, MongDB, MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL

Please contact me to discuss more regarding project.
Thanks.