⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ 5-Stars Rating for all of my Projects.
Let's make "Success" Together!
☀ The way a page appears and the design of the website that users see and interact with may make your business fall or grow!
Enthusiastic Front-End Developer who loves to create effective websites and work with businesses to help them grow.
✨ My skills:
I consider myself a person who follows modern web development practices and new technologies.
So, this list will be uniformly updated as I never stop learning.
⚡MERN Stack(MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js)
⚡REACT/REDUX/HOOK, Angular
⚡HTML/HTML5
⚡CSS/CSS3
⚡SASS/SCSS Preprocessor
⚡ Responsive Web Design.
⚡JAVASCRIPT/ES6
⚡ PHP, Laravel, Codeigniter, ZendFramework, Drupal.
⚡APIs/JSON/AJAX
⚡GITHUB
⚡MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Database Programming.

✨ Personal Qualities:
⚡A clean responsive code that will be well displayed in any browser and adapted to any device of any resolution, be it a phone or a tablet, or a widescreen device.
⚡ Fast response and good communication skills.
⚡ well-organized/commented code.
⚡ SEO friendly, semantic markup, and load speed optimization.
⚡Testing and cross-browser / cross-device compatibility.

The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing. -Walt Disney

Thank you.